hello everyone
my name is ombati wujanji
a financial consultant with prudential
life insurance ghana and this
is my success story i joined prudential
life insurance ghana in
2018 after being introduced to the
business by madame dorothy chidi
when she mentioned the opportunities
prudential life gave to its agents
during one of my trainings at the bank
ambitious as i am
i was curious about the opportunities
available for me should i join the team
and decided to find out more about it
mr thief lost intel gave me all the
necessary details i needed to make an
informed decision
courageously i went in for the interview
and training session and that marked the
beginning of my journey
in less than six months
as a result of me being nimble on the
job
i won my first award
[Applause]
an all expense paid weekend to soutomi
and it was a great experience
with all its highs and lows i have
learned to work in and with a team
and this has served as a source of
motivation for me
taught me about conflict resolution and
helped me to improve upon being
empathetic
in my dealings with both prospective and
existing clients that i come into
contact with
several recognitions and awards have
been received since then
and it's been an interesting journey
with a flexible working hours
top-notch training
multiple streams of income and several
incentives
with a clear-cut career path prudential
life continues to be a good fit for me
i would like to take this opportunity to
thank god almighty
for the opportunity given to be part
of this company
and then to my family friends and loved
ones for the encouragement and
motivation
prudential life insurance ghana
continues to be a good fit for my career
so i urge you to take advantage of the
numerous opportunities available thank
you